three-day weekend. Uh the final, I would
say, uh true day of summertime before we
have to get going on things. Uh
going to try to get through this one
relatively quickly. So
the empowerment through AI side, I I I
do want to make sure you guys realize as
we go into the final four months of the
year, we've hit the most important point
in AI where the AI agents are growing
rapidly. Um, this is really as much for
anyone who's working at a job that
doesn't know how to use AI from a
workflow perspective yet. Uh, the time
is gone. So, I do these videos and I go
through this really to help people to
educate them and to help them through
the empowerment of making money. But if
you understand how to use AI from an
agentic perspective and you understand
crypto, which is what the focus is, you
are at the most important part of the
disruption. And if not you, at least
your your kids. I have great
relationships and I've built them in
terms of people that have had their kids
call out. I can't take all the calls of
everyone who reaches out saying, "Will
you speak to my my son, my daughter for
uh 30 minutes? I don't have the time,
guys. It's a oneman show. I'm busy. I
know a lot of you are reaching out more
and more more if I don't respond to your
emails or I don't get to things. You
have to understand I get so many. So,
I'm going to go through this video, but
I want to make sure that you guys
realize as you look at the first chart,
well, not the first one. Remember, I
can't guarantee that I'll make you
money. This is not advice. This is a
educational show. The disclosures are
there. This is what I want you guys to
understand. Um,
you believe many of you in your head
that your kid goes to a good school,
they work really hard, they end up
getting a a job, they get a raise every
year, they save, and they retire. That
is not the way the world works anymore
for the majority of people. And I don't
think it'll be the way that it works for
anyone. The new world, and I've talked
to you about my son and what's going on,
is this. It is the ability of learning
anywhere at any time. I have this
conversation with so many adults. I have
been given such a gift. I love learning.
I love being creative. I love being a
critical thinker. My brain has never
felt more powerful than today because
whenever I want to learn something or
build on something, I'm working with AI,
but now with agents. So, first it was
typing things. Then it was chatting and
having conversations and collaborating
together. But now it's sending them off
to build things, to come back, have a
staff meeting, all of that stuff. Maybe
it's because I manage people for a long
time. But every young person should be
able to do this. And that's the way
they're going to have empowerment. If
they learn how to use AI and they learn
how to use agents, they can build their
own business. If they build their own
business, they can build five
businesses. If they build five
businesses, the question is how do they
invest? By understanding crypto,
tokenization, tokenized products. Trust
me, their ability to invest and make 20%
a year will blow you away. Not through
speculating, not through betting on
football, but actually through having
agents build a tokenized portfolio of
things that are diversified where you
can get a good sharp ratio. I'll go
through that. Pay attention to that.
This week's major theme, stop with the
bond fears. Everyone in X, everyone in
there, the same people who were saying
AI is a bubble are telling you that the
bond market is going to explode higher
and it's going to create problems. Is
there a chance that yields will go up?
Yes. Do I think they could go to five
and a half, 10 year yields? Sure. Do I
think Scott Besson is going to fight it?
Absolutely, he's going to fight it. He's
already shown that. Why do I want to be
involved in something that can go from
here to here when it just went from here
to here and it's been in a range that's
been nothing? This is all throughout X
and every technician and everyone who's
bearish just keeps rolling out these
bond fears. 30-year yields are going to
make the highest level. We're at 523. We
could make the highest level since 2004
very soon. Guys, don't believe the hype.
I'll tell you why. Here's what Bonval is
doing. If this was really a crisis,
trust me, bonvs would be up here. They
wouldn't be sitting down here. For
anyone who wants to tell you, whoa, they
wouldn't be there. And if it wasn't
Bonval, then okay, how about this? How
about junk spreads wouldn't be sitting
at the tightest level ever. Junk
spreads. Now, triple C's are widening
out, which again, as I've said, I think
you're going to see spreads kind of
widen out because I think you're going
to see a lot of places go out of
business because of AI. Here are
inflation swaps. two or one year, two
year, 5year, 10 year. Here are the
numbers from 249 or 248 to 252.
They're not only at 2 and a half where
they've been since 2022.
They're all at the exact same level,
which happens to be where core CPI is as
well. There's core CPI 248. By the way,
here's the daily trueflation number. I
don't care what you believe in true
inflation. Do not listen to anyone that
says this has no value. That is not
true. It absolutely has value. The fact
that it is deviating in falling this
fast to me, I I I'm curious as to what's
going on inside their prices because
they are calculated on real prices. The
scary bond chart. Here's the reality.
This is the fact that chart with yields
going higher. Here's the total return if
you invested in 20 plus years. So not
even 10 year. This is the worst one. 20
years and above, your return this year
minus 3%. Here's what it was in 2022
when it actually mattered, down 32%.
JGB 30-year yields. May of last year, we
broke out to all-time highs. You want to
see the damage that's been done since
then as 117 basis points. May 20th, Zero
Hedge doing one of their let me scare
you things. The biggest bond market is
imploding. Here's where the Nikai was
that day. Here's where it's gone.
Here's where the Nikkei is
year-over-year, up 52%. So, if you
listen to this garbage, you cost
yourself a 70% rally in that time
period.
Here's what Robin Brooks wrote this
week. This is a rational person. This
selloff is ongoing since 2022. So, this
is not something new. As he says, we've
been going higher.
It won't spin out of control into a
crisis because governments won't let it.
You do you believe that? Of course you
do. You have to. We're seeing signs of
it at this point. They don't want it to
go higher. They will try to find ways to
keep it in check. Now, this has got
Japan. This has got Germany. This has
got the US. This has got the UK. It's
got all of these stock markets are still
going higher, but they're all there.
This is Switzerland. So, he highlights
this is all about the level of debt.
It's not a crisis. It's about the fact
there's a lot of debt and growth is
good. This selloff is completely global.
Governments everywhere are fighting
this. Inflation break evens are fast
asleep everywhere. Like I said, those
are the facts. Here's another fact.
Besson expects Japan to act to boost
yen. We saw the yen again this week.
Strengthen.
I know what the Japanese are planning to
do, says Bessant. We're in coordination.
It's not just one country. They're all
involved in this, or at least Japan and
the US are. Here's the PEG ratio, the
S&P. So, now let's get to the facts. Do
you really want to focus on the bond
thing with what I just showed you? We've
been going higher. None of the other
places, the bond VA, any of that stuff
is showing any risk. Okay, here's the
S&P PEG ratio. And again, the PEG ratio
means what's the forward PE? Let's
assume it's 20 right now. The what's the
earnings growth rate? Let's assume it's
25 right now.
Okay, so the earnings growth rate right
here is higher than the PE. So you have
a PEG ratio down here. This is at the
lowest level since 198. You cannot say
that the market is expensive and it's a
bubble unless you're saying this is a
bubble and is going to collapse. You
want to say that, that's great. You're
just going against charts that are
incredibly powerful. And here are the
revisions. We just came out of an
earnings period. the weekly revisions
through the roof. And as I've said
before, the time to be short stocks is
when the red stuff, 2022, when rates
were going higher.
This is when you wanted to be bearish on
stocks. When the Fed chair is saying,
"Don't own stocks. We don't care." Now
you have the president saying, "I don't
want rates higher." You have Besson
saying, "I don't want rates higher. We
want to run it hot. We want stocks
higher." Here are the revisions.
companies are still earning. Here it is
with GDP, meaning forward GDP as PMIs
PMIs continue to sit. And again, they're
not at 60. We got the PMI out to
manufacturing. It's at 55 revisions.
This is the 20week average of revisions.
Now, let's go through the facts on the
stocks. Leading indicator, when you want
to be bearish, like you were in '08, we
get a recession signal here. We get a
recession signal here. We're up 18%
year-over-year in the S&P. The NASDAQ
were up 24% year-over-year. The Russell
were up 23% year-over-year. SMH
Semiconductors where a lot of
bubbleistas are. They still believe this
is coming all the way to zero. I see the
technicians. I see what they're talking
about. Ignore them. 88%.
Here are global revisions. If you think
this is a US problem in terms of being
strong, no. Globe. Good.
This is coming out of recession periods
or coming out of the crash in 16 with
oil where we got things higher. Again,
the globe is good. MCI World up 16%
year-over-year.
MSCI Emerging Markets up 30%
MSCI World Bank Index, if there was a
problem in bonds and there was a problem
in credit, banks would not be doing
well. Banks led the S&P down in ' 07.
Banks end up being horrible during
periods in Europe during the Europe. We
got no problems right now. Banks are up
29% year-over-year.
Let's go look at revenues per share in
the Aqu going through the roof.
Revisions going through the roof.
Earnings and valuation with inside the
bands at below 20. And it's because
earnings are going higher.
There's the earnings per share. Again, I
got to take this down because we're
going off the chart. All right, let's
keep my head there for a little bit.
There's profit margins. I mean, do you
really want to focus on the bond market
when you have profit margins around the
globe going up this much? Shouldn't long
equities be a better thing? Looks Look
what happens before a recession, guys.
Look, you at least get a flattening out
a year, two years before.
You don't get this.
Here's the scary oil chart. Another
scary chart. A lot of people talked
about oil this week because we went
through on this is December contract.
Well, the Fed's got to raise rates.
Yeah, there they might raise 25 basis
points. I'm really going to be scared of
a 25 basis point rise. Um, if you want
to avoid stocks because of a 25 basis
point while earnings are growing, profit
margins are growing. Okay, here's oil up
at $86. And again, as I've shown before,
the year-over-year oil price for the
sixth contract forward is up 22%.
It should always be up at least this
much during times that the economy is
good. Always
spending still happening. So, if you're
worried about the economy, the Johnson
Redbook, the fiveweek year-over-year
average is at 9.6. So, we had the World
Cup, went up, then we came down. Here's
what the last week was in August all the
way back up to here. Here's what the
overlay is with personal spending.
Obviously, consumption is 67% of the US
economy. All right, here we are. And
here's the white line, Johnson Redbook.
S&P, you really want to be bearish now
when we finally had a correction for the
first time this year since the Iran war
where the S&P was up 20% over a rolling
three-month basis because of the AI
trade. The AI trade peaks. I send you
guys the AI midcycle slowdown. The S&P
goes down, go starts to go through it.
Here we are in July around the point
where Liupole blows up. The S&P hit the
zero line, which means the threemonth
rate of change got to zero and now we've
bounced out. AI is bottoming as well in
my opinion, which I'll show you. The
advanced decline, another way to use it.
I used the 9-day RSI in this. We hit the
25 level. That's where we were at the
lows in March. See what happens. Most
importantly, the number one stock for
the AI trade is Nvidia. Most important,
every chip stock follows Nvidia because
they're the one this the head of the
circular finance. They are the ones
paying everyone. They are the ones that
need all of their stuff. So, if their
stock is breaking out, do you really
want to call semiconductors a bubble? Do
you really want to fall for that, guys?
Here's Nvidia approaching new all-time
highs. And since Chat GBT came out in
2022, this is the overlay with the S&P.
I don't think you want to be bearish
stocks when Nvidia is about to make new
all-time highs. Here's Nvidia overlaid
with the socks again. Nvidia peaked
here. Semis peaked here. I just think
you're making a mistake right now. If
you're sitting there listening to
technicians and people scaring you with
rate charts, ask yourself this. If a
technician is bearish on semiconductors,
go see if they're bullish on yields. If
you're getting the same thing and
they've written and called this a
bubble. If they're also bearish on
Bitcoin, there might be a thing here
where they're developing an endgame bias
like I talked about two weeks ago. I'm
showing you guys the facts of the
market. Is the SMH below the 50-day
moving average and is it trending down?
Yes. Nvidia is up here. So, I'm giving
you a fact up here. Until this breaks
here and actually breaks here, I think
you can continue to say that we're
there. As I'm going to show you and as I
went through last week, I think this
stuff is bottoming after this. This to
me is a consolidation. People don't
think moves like this consolidate. I
believe they do.
S&P
here's where the chart finished the
week. It's not bearish. And this is
again, this is where we were in June.
Here we are in September. Basically
unchanged. Q's again, I don't see this
as bearish. Russell, I don't see this as
bearish. All of these are above the 200
day moving average and significantly
above. They needed to have some time to
to let the 200 day come higher. I got a
lot of things this week on tech
momentum. Everyone's panicked because
they made new lows in this. Here is the
long side of momentum. This is not the
same as what was going on here. Trust
me, I will show you some stats on this.
This is about the long side going up and
deleveraging continue to happen. That is
what caused this. The shorts going up
caused this. This has nothing to do with
reality. This has to do, this is not
earnings. This is not anything. This
continued to be deleveraging. And as I
said here, we can't just go back to the
highs. I believe this stuff is stuck in
mud. Do I think we're going to get to
the highs? Yes. Do I think it's going to
take time? Yes. Here's my thematic
portfolio. So again, when we break the
50-day here, I still expect it to go to
here and pause. And my guess is by the
time we go higher, it's probably after
the midterms. I don't think this is the
place to be making lots of money. But
this is the place where I did make buys
in this period for Micron and stuff like
that because
I do believe that a year now we're going
to be much higher. Most of my waitings
are towards crypto and I continue to add
to crypto. Here is the internals of my
thematic portfolio. This stuff going
forward I'm only going to show in the
crypto portion. So I've decided what to
do is this video will remain on YouTube.
It's open to everyone but for people who
want my thematic portfolio and the
crypto side to understand this part
along with the prompts and everything.
The subscribers will have that and I
will do more work on this and I will add
the crypto side into it. This is the
thing that I showed last week. So here
in this week, the thing that stands out
to me, we had two weeks in a row where
the number of names with inside the 100
uh portfolio didn't hold where we had
this. We had two weeks of kind of blah.
This was a bad week following this made
sense. It was better last week. It was
better again this week. This is the most
important part. If you guys have not
used ATR percent, the average true range
of a 100 names, this is taking the
average 14-day true range of each
individual stock.
This thing is going lower. This is a
very positive sign because this means
hedge funds are not getting stopped
anymore. Retail is not involved anymore.
This happens because of stops. This
happens because the need to move things
through force things whether it's margin
or everything is expanding. This is why
this is such an important signal and
very few people use it. Here's the chart
of it. It was going higher as the market
was going higher. This was part of the
reason that I was reducing things back
in here is because V was going higher in
these names which meant people were
either speculating more, putting things
on or getting stopped out and then it
continued to move higher during the
stopout period. Well, now it's going
down every single week. This is the
number weekly. Here's the overlay with
the thematic portfolio. So, we went up,
this thing was coming down. It continued
to go down during this slide. Now, we're
seeing this. I believe the bottom is in
back here and I think the thematic AI
portfolio the stuff that I go through is
going to go higher. I will start doing
some spotlight pieces again and I will
start going through the names that I
like. I've told you repeatedly since I
don't know if it was in here whatever
but in in this point but Nvidia is one
of the names and now because of its
recent move it's as big as Marll for me.
I believe Nvidia is a good place to be
while we're stuck in the mud. it made
the low the same time it's up at
all-time highs. So, this is a relative
strength thing relative to my thematic
portfolio. Part of the reason that I
want you guys to understand that when
people get worried about semiconductors
in the AI trade because of rates,
they're way off base. Interest rates are
a rounding error on inference P&L. So,
what three companies matter the most?
The three companies that matter the most
are Anthropic, OpenAI, and Nvidia.
Those are the ones that matter the most.
Nvidia is the one selling the
semiconductors to the people that need
to get their money from the compute
demand which is being done mainly
through anthropic and open AI which are
dominating the models. The revenue per
token this is it this whole thing is
based on the interest rate impact. It
actually goes through everything. So
model price what's the most important
part for open AAI and for anthropic you
should know this rates are irrelevant.
So a 10% model price decline is worth
three percentage points of margin. 10%
model price. So again, 26 down to 23.4.
Great. Interest rates a 200 basis point
rise. So in 10ear yields from 5 to 7,
that's only one margin point. Here it is
right here. So again for open AAI they
can keep paying for this and that keeps
the compute prices high which allows
again Nvidia to continue to spend money
and make money and that allows Dell and
Marll and Micron and all these companies
to still not have to worry about things
that is the circular nature. So
remember, if you have a concentrated
economy, which we do, the three
companies that matter are Anthropic,
OpenAI, and Nvidia, is there a chance
that something could go wrong? Yeah, the
risks are model price compression.
That's not happening yet. So again,
until we get to that point, the hardware
costs don't matter. the infant, none of
this stuff is going to matter as much if
the model price collapses, which again,
it's not going to happen in my opinion
anytime soon because they have the best
models. And as I go through this, you'll
see why that's important. Nvidia blows
out the quarter, stock trades lower,
goes right back up. Very positive sign.
Dell surges 9% after good numbers. So,
good numbers are being rewarded. The
computer maker now sees AI server
revenue tripling. Six months ago, it
expected it only to double.
Germany, this is not a US problem.
You're starting to see other countries
are running short of AI compute.
Welcome to the AGI era. If you guys have
not read the things about Astra, Astra
[clears throat] is now officially the
best model in the world on the
benchmarks. The scary part is we are at
the point and the reason this article is
on AGI is because we've reached the
point on there where it can basically do
every knowledge worker job. That's how
good it's gotten and that's where this
is. About a year ago, I think we were
around the 40% level. We're now at 100.
We are at the agentic side and that's
what AGI stands for is artificial
general intelligence. Their definition
is when is it smart enough to replace
all jobs, do all jobs. It won't be
rolled out that way. We're not going to
see all these job losses, but we are at
a different stage. The most important
podcast for you guys to listen to, if
you pick one for this week, absolutely
listen to the artificial intelligence
show, the one they did called Open Face,
uh, Open AI Hugging Face. You need to
understand what's going on. And this
open AI hugging face thing, I had so
many people reach out. I had very very
uh well-known people reach out
specifically on this and again my
opinion on this is it's part hype and
it's part reality of the agentic side.
It's not a negative thing. There will be
hackings. I say it every week on this
show. There will be significant hackings
in the traditional fiat world, not in
crypto. Will there be hackings in apps
in crypto? Of course. Will there be
crypto or Bitcoin hacks? No, not not not
till we get to quantum, but this was not
just a hack story. This was about how
agents are working, how smart they are,
and where we are. And this was using
supposedly Astra. So, you have to listen
to what they describe. They read through
some reports which came out and released
over the week that got everyone excited
and worried. Some agents actually
sacrificed their own goals for the
collective. I talked about this with
Pomp today. This is amazing because I've
managed hundreds of people. I I can't
remember a time where someone's willing
to sacrifice their job for the
betterment of everyone else. They might
sacrifice in terms of something. But the
difference between AI agents and why
this is so powerful is because they're
working in teams of 1,200
to accomplish a goal. That's where we
are now with the swarm. You have to pay
attention to this because this changes
the mental model from AI assistant to AI
organization. This is exactly the moment
in time where crypto matters. Browser
agents matter. Now, if you don't know
how to go in, they tell you what you
need to do in codeex. You have no time
to wait anymore. As a worker, as an
employee, as a college student, you have
to be able to do this now. If you want
to stay in the top 5%, don't try to get
an A on every paper. try to know how to
do this. My son has already proved in
the success of his side and what he's
been able to build. You can do this,
especially as a 21-year-old to 22 year
old, but even a 16-year-old. For all of
you parents that reach out and want me
to talk to your child, I would love to
be able to do that. I don't have the
time. I'm a one-man band, except for
Mark Whailing that's helped me. It's me,
guys. For business leader, it becomes
the workflow design. So, if you're at a
big company or an RAIA and you're
telling me that you're using Anthropic,
you're falling behind. That's what this
says. If your major plan is to give
everyone Anthropic, you are falling
behind. That's not a joke. That is a
reality. We are on AI agents now. We are
past all of that stuff. So, if you're
not focusing on how to have workflows
redesigned and you're just giving people
tools, your business is going to be
slower than the AI native ones that are
running with this. You can call me up
but at a minimum you have to start
subscribing to this. I will do a
presentation for your FAS. People need
to start using it and that is the reason
for the prompts but this is the mindset
you have to listen to this podcast to
start for families for your educations
for your careers. Like I said they go
through Bill Gates he he published
something where he shifted and again I
hate perma anybody. I hate perma bulls.
I hate perma bears. If you can't be
serious and talk about both sides of the
equation, what value do you bring? So, I
just don't listen. The reason this is an
important thing is from Bill Gates is
because he shifted his view. He shifted
his view because agents have now entered
and he they are moving so fast that
there is no way that we can keep people
on the other side. People can't adopt it
as fast as being replaced. This will
become normal now. So, the only way to
defend yourself is to learn how to use
it while you're at the job and do it at
home. There's ways to learn. The
takeaway from all of this is not panic.
It's time to prepare both for AI but
also for crypto. That is what this is.
This is the new world and the next three
years are going to be insane. On this
podcast, they talk about how OpenAI and
Enthropic are telling you that the next
year will be worth four years of AI
progress. The last four years is the AI
progress, guys. That's chat GPT to AI
agents. It took a long time to get here.
Now, it's accelerating at such a fast
pace that a year from now, it will blow
your mind. Three years from now with
humanoids, it'll blow your mind. If
you're doubting it, if you just go into
action, you go, "Yeah, yeah, you're just
talking about stuff that's never going
to happen." That's not helping you and
it's not helping your children. And I'm
just telling you, as someone who got
into finance as the son of a
construction worker who didn't want to
siphon gas with his mouth, who didn't
want to get electrocuted, who didn't
want to have no hearing, who didn't want
to I was handed a book and it was the
power of compounding. I'm going to tell
you again and again, crypto plus
tokenization will allow you to take the
money that you're making and not save
it, compound it. The days of saving your
money and having your 401k go at 10% was
about a world where you could start at
20,000 and then you go to 50,000 and you
go to 100 and your 401k would help you.
Those were days in the 1980s, 1990s.
We've been running into this problem
which is why everyone is barely making
money on they're not actually making and
saving and having money work for them.
Crypto and tokenization will allow you
to do this. Gavin Baker podcast. Another
one. I'm not going to give you
everything on this, but I am going to
say this part from 1715 to 2034.
Grockbot style agents are described as a
new consumption shock. That is the
critical part right there. From chatbots
to agents. Again, most of you are still
stuck in this area. If you've actually
started using Claude code and you've
been doing coding assisting and you've
been building some of the things that I
put in there, for those of you who built
the Jensen Yuang knowledge brain and I
said if you build this, this will open a
gateway. Many of you have reached out
and talked about multiple brains you
built, including mine
that if you haven't done that yet, sign
up. Go to the subscriber thing. And by
the way, I'm not putting anything in
this on this. Go to VisseryLabs.
Visser-labs.com.
You can get to the site, but I gave
people in there a prompt for building a
Jensen Senuang knowledge brain. Last
week, I gave you a Grockpot prompt.
These prompts once you start using them
and you know how to do them, they lead
to this one, which is the personal
workflow agent to read, to summarize,
compare, recommend, ask permission. This
is where we are now. The compute needs
on this massively more than what's over
here.
financial agents, you will be blown away
by what's going to happen. And this is
where the crypto side comes in. So this
is the merging happening right here. We
had to get the IQ up to get to this
point. Then we went to the coding
agents, but now we're in the personal
and the workflow agents. That means we
need financial agents and that's what's
beginning to happen now. And that's
where crypto fits in. And that's why
crypto is rallying.
X's AI tool, Grock, now allows users to
buy or lend crypto with Moonay
integration. So again, I'm highlighting
the fact that every week there's a new
thing with Grockbot being integrated.
Grockbot, Stripe can now purchase
anywhere with Link. If you haven't tried
Grockbot, you should. It's very good. It
can now buy things on the internet.
Here's what I'm giving you this week. So
the agentic or the yeah the agentic 100
name thematic portfolio which I'm saying
in my opinion is bottoming and starting
to go higher again building a base. If I
want to go look for names that are in
there I wanted to create something in
Grockbot. So I created more agents. So
Jarvis, I sat down with Jarvis and I
said I want to do something new and I
want you to create the agents that go
through. So it created new agents
created pattern scout. created universe
clerk
and now we're uploading this. This is a
daily postclo chart pattern screen of
the AI macro nexus 100 in Grockpot. So
this will use Yahoo Finance. It will go
into Yahoo Finance and it will look for
all 100 names in the IO macro nexus
book, scan each chart for classical
bullish and bearish patterns and then it
will tell you what's changed today every
day. That's what this will do. So this
way you can go if you want to trade
names and you want to find things that
are positive and the ones you should go
do your own technical work in. I'm not
telling you to buy anything. I'm showing
you how you can use this and then
incorporate it in the way that you guys
look at it. That's the way you can do
it. April of last or April of this year,
Mark Andre gave a podcast. I didn't show
this. It's in uh latent space around
April 4th. I I didn't show it back then,
but I listened to it. Um I remember I
was in LA or I just come back. The
reason I didn't show it is because
everything he talked about to me that
was important was basically from the
50inute mark to the 55. Agents were
happening but it wasn't happening with
payments yet. So it was a crypto thing
for me. AI is the crypto killer app.
Basically his point AI is the crypto
killer app. It's the app that makes
crypto start to blow up. It's gets it's
the crypto side. Crypto is not made for
human beings. The first phase of crypto
was all about developing it to be
something embraced by humans. But
eventually AI agents needed the digital
payments. They needed stable coins. They
didn't need Bitcoin. They needed
tokenization. They didn't need Bitcoin.
Bitcoin is part of the ecosystem. Which
is why I show you guys how Bitcoin
equals the ecosystem. It always will.
Just like the S&P 500 equals the EOS
ecosystem of the US economy. The agent
economy is Bitcoin. plain and simple for
me. You guys don't have to agree, but
that's just a reality for me. I've
proved it to myself and I've gone
through this. The early internet never
solved native payments. Andre says
payments will get solved now because
crypto exists. He's saying if crypto
wasn't before agents, we wouldn't be
there. Crypto had to happen, which is
why he wrote the paper or the op-ed in
2014 called Why Bitcoin Matters. It was
all about these things. This is not
something new for him. He was preparing
for this day. This is the grand
unification or the merge of AI and
crypto. It's why I say Bitcoin is the
purest AI hedge. It works because AI
destroys all businesses. All businesses.
You don't need human beings. So new
businesses will have five people, 10
people. They will be small. They will
grow from nothing. Which is why you have
to have an entrepreneurial mindset. And
your kids have to learn how to do that.
They have to be entrepreneurs. They have
to fail and they have to get back up.
You know what that's like? Trading.
That's why I'm doing this stuff. They
have to get involved with crypto, with
tokenization, with understanding AI
because it's about building something,
it not working, getting another name,
building it again. You have to come up
with idea after idea after idea. And
going into a classroom and listening to
a boring professor who's telling you one
person's opinion will not get you there.
AI will allow you to talk with a hundred
agents, whatever you want.
The grand unification crypto's mass
market use case may not start with
humans wanting to use. It needs agents.
Agents obviously need money. The future
is already here. The joke hides in
serious risk. Agents need financial
guard rails. Mark Andre is the man for
this. And this is the way to look at it.
Not humans, but AI agents will be the
biggest users of crypto. So think about
that. If you believe that crypto volumes
are going to explode, that everything is
going to be tokenized and that AI agents
will be the biggest users of crypto,
that means we are about to see billions
of consumers. So, what I want you to do
is equate crypto
to tokens. As token usage happen, what
happened to the AI infrastructure?
What's going to happen to the crypto
infrastructure? Regardless of what
happens with the Clarity Act, it doesn't
matter. The only reason it matters is
because if the US wants to remain the
leader in something, they have to have
the Clarity Act to get the capital from
the pension funds and from the insurance
companies.
All Clarity does is give the regulation
and basically the seal of approval for
pension funds and for people to go,
okay, crypto is now accepted on this
form. They're still going to be involved
in Bitcoin and things like that, but to
involve themselves in the market, they
can't worry that all of a sudden a new
administration is going to take over and
they're going to put crypto backwards by
four years again. I don't think that's
going to happen, but that's the risk.
Crypto didn't lack a use case. It lacked
a native user. AI creates it. So, here
are the charts. Bitcoin
up to the technical level I mentioned
and showed. We're hanging in. We're
consolidating. We're doing a great thing
here. We have this big gigantic raise
here. And then we have this sideways
action, very bullish. And in dinners I
went to this week and in talking to
people, both who've been, I'd say, major
winners in Bitcoin or in crypto. And
then people that are active in it and
regular people on the street that I run
into,
the ideologues don't believe in it
nearly as much. So they've bailed out or
they've reduced significantly. That's my
silent IPO the thesis. The other side is
most people did not catch this move
because of the frustration that had gone
on here and they didn't want to fall
into it. The they were asking if it's
going to fall back to the 60s. Most
people believe this was going to bottom
in October. It seems to be getting away.
I don't think you're going to get the
chance. That's just me. Here's Ethereum
again. The 200 day turned up in Bitcoin.
It also turned up here. I went through
the numbers last week based on history.
This is a great time to be involved in
these chartwise. It's a great time.
Here's Salana. These are the three
horsemen that I'll be showing every week
on the crypto side along with the crypto
portfolio of 46, a combination of six
stocks and 40 tokens. It might grow, it
might change. I'm working on what it's
going to go through, but that video will
start at sometime this month. Um, so
Salana, same thing. 200 day is now
pointed upward and we're trading higher
and we're consolidating at this level.
If you want to know what quartertoate
performance is, if you haven't been in
crypto, and remember I told you I've
been I had been started rotating in May
into June, out of Micron, out of these
things. My AI stuff is smaller than
crypto by a good amount, especially when
you beta adjust it. So, it's been a very
good time for the Jordy portfolio since
June. Most of it happening here. But
here are the quarterly returns to date.
So, this is what you're dealing with if
you're sitting there at a mutual fund,
at an asset management, at a hedge fund,
and you're not trading this. Ethereum up
56% quarter to date. Salana up 38.
Bitcoin up 36. The S&P 500 up three,
NASDAQ down three, SMH down 14. Do I
think these are going higher between now
and the end of the year? Yes. But I'm
going to tell you, earnings are growing
at 30% a year. These things are growing
at half of that. This is my double
debasement story. I'm gonna keep saying
it. Crypto is going to take a high
percentage of the fiat asset over the
course of the next five years because of
the disruption from AI and the need for
the government to prevent rates from
going higher and to make sure that the
K-shaped economy is kept in check. Robin
Hood stock soarses thanks to Wall
Street. Robin Hood is part of the 46name
crypto portfolio.
If you didn't read what happened, they
were upgraded by multiple places and one
of the reasons is because of their new
layer 2 chain. So they are heavily
involved in stock token trades. So we
are already in tokenization. In just six
weeks, a billion a half dollars trades
sounded like science fiction two years
ago. Here are the numbers. Looks kind of
like the token expansion in AI. Look at
this happening now. Okay. All in August.
Here's the RWA market. The reason I
wanted to show this, this is growing
too. And it's grown 18 times. Now, the
real world asset market has mainly been
the building of the collateral here with
the stuff that Black Rockck has done,
the things that uh Franklin Templeton
has done, all Tro all of these places.
But they're doing money market funds.
They're gradually getting into things.
This is the collateral in there. This
was the first phase. Now we're starting
to get into not just tokenized stocks,
tokenized equity for sports teams. South
Korea is saying they'll be ready by or
starting 2027, February 4th. This is not
a US thing. I showed Japan last week.
South Korea, this is a race now to make
sure that you're still involved in
capital. If you haven't read anything
about PERS, here's something from a A16Z
uh crypto. You have to start reading
this stuff and start realizing this. The
catalyst for this was Iran. The catalyst
for this was SpaceX and Anthropic
perpetual futures. The ability to trade
things 247 365. The ability to not have
to deal with roles on futures. You have
to understand this stuff because all of
these financial innovations are
happening. Here's where we are now. The
tokenization roadmap. Legacy finance
before tokenization. This old slow
system. Crypto smart contracts are
basically created.
All of these things are value. Then we
get into the bridge being built. Tradfi
goes, "Okay, we're here. The government
accepts it. Now we're going to start
getting into this over the next 12
months and then into 2030. This is where
crypto benefits dramatically." This is
where portfolios, wallets, everything
starts to happen. And you have a
decentralized, democratized ability of
ownership where you can go buy something
that is small. you can go buy anything,
IP trades, all of this. This is a
completely different world. So, this is
not something that you can sit there
like with AI and be like, "Okay, I
understand it. I I guess you have to put
the work in." And that's what I'll be
spending the time. And that's what I've
been doing myself for all of this time.
This is the reason I chose not to go to
a hedge fund. It was because I didn't
want to manage people. I didn't want to
work for investors. I didn't want to
work for management. I didn't want to go
through that anymore. But I also believe
that I could be an entrepreneur and I
could make the money I'm making and
benefit from AI and crypto, which is
what's been going on. This is why I talk
to you guys on this. I'm not stuck
behind a desk forced to do certain
stupid things and not be able to use the
tools. I can use every AI tool, and I do
use every AI tool. I have multiple
computers, multiple Mac minis. I
understand crypto far more than I did
two years ago. So that's why people
reach out to me and that's why I'm
telling you right now is the time the
convergence is happening. Not three
months ago, not six months. That's why
those charts look like that.
Tokenization is growing now. I just
showed you the Robin Hood stable coin
that the RA Robin Hood onchain that's
happening now. AI trades stuck in the
mud. We've seen V explode in the AI
names. They've already had their run
from this point. There's all kinds of
risk associated with Micron. Do I think
it'll double between now and the and
next year? Probably. But a doubles not
10 times. That trade has already
happened. Policy wants it higher and
they want rates in check. We just
started to see this with the yen side
the same week as the AI trade gets stuck
in the mud or ends up blowing up with
Liupold. The tape breaks out on the back
of this. Then we have the rise of agents
beginning. I show you Astra. I show you
Grockbot. They're all happening now. And
the governments are if clarity act gets
voted through. I think you're going to
see an immediate next leg to this. You
have to be ready for this. The G20
talked about it. The Jackson Hole
Symposium. It was throughout that. This
is not just a US thing. Best involved
around the globe. I know what the
Japanese are planning on doing.
Robin Brooks, bond yields are going
higher. I wrote this paper. The age of
abundant intelligence and scarce
Bitcoin. Two presses running at once.
This is the key to crypto. This is the
key for you to pay attention to. We are
seeing multiple impression in the S&P
500 because of AI. Terminal value is
being changed. So PE's come down. At the
same time, the government is in there
debasing. Don't listen to people saying
inflation's running too hot. The Fed has
to go on a tightening cycle and all this
stuff. The market's not saying that
right now. If it was going to happen and
the market was worried about it, we'd
see it. Earnings are growing rapidly.
This is what happens. And now we have
crypto starting the move. Until we break
out, we haven't gone through it. Once we
get above 82 and we're above there, I
think there's going to be a chase
factor, particularly as you go through
this. The Fed meeting has now taken on
extreme importance because if the market
trades higher after the Fed raises
rates, I don't think it's going to stop
from that point. If they don't do
anything, then I think you're gonna see
the market trade higher. So, right now,
because it's already built into the
market, I think you're playing a game
here with the midterm seasonality. Um,
in this paper, I talk about the double
debasement. I talk about the printing
intelligence. I'm bringing that up so
you guys can go read it. You can catch
up if you haven't paid attention. These
are all substacks. These are all out
there. All of my writings in crypto will
now be part of the subscriber side. I
will do one a month for the loyal sub uh
substack people that have been there.
So, I will release one a month. That'll
be a thematic thing similar to this, but
the majority of my papers are going to
be on the subscriber payw wall. Um, the
silent IPO is over. Bitcoin AI and the
Collision of Time. I highly recommend
reading this one. This is the one I
wrote on the first week of August.
Handicapping the future. This one goes
through how I think about Bitcoin and
how I've gone through to think about
converting it into probability. So, I'm
going to end this here. For those of you
who don't know, my father trained me in
handicapping horses. He told me not to
look he told me to not look for the
winner. Always look for value. If there
is no edge in the race, sit it out. So
what that means is if I find something
that I think is 100 to one, which is
what I think Bitcoin is. It's not just a
winner. I don't need to put that much
money in something that's 100 to1 to
have a great payoff. That's the way I've
approached it. Annie Duke, the edge is
in disciplined thinking. If you believe
in bit, don't believe in Bitcoin today
and you didn't believe in it 10 years
and you haven't thought about it or gone
through it, you're not being disciplined
in your thinking. Charlie Munger said,
"The world was a paramutual system,
which means you can convert everything
back into odds because it reflects
people's positioning. Prices reflect how
capital's position. The crowd sets the
odds." I believe that mispricing appears
when the crowd misses something. I'm
showing you what I think the crowd is
missing. They're not using AI. The
people that have most of the world's
money and they don't believe in crypto.
They're missing what's happening. They
don't understand it, which is fine. It
creates the opportunity. Paul Tudtor
Jones, great trade start before
consensus. That is my third wave start.
That is where I believe in Elliot wave
terms. Great trade start before
consensus. Right now, people are
depressed. Both people that have been
there, the ideologues and the silent
IPO. You don't have to agree with me on
this, but I'm giving you my thesis and
laying out how I approach it. Stan, good
idea. No positioning equals opportunity.
Perfect. This is where I think we are
right now. Size the bet without blowing
up. So that gets into the probability.
So this is the way I'm going to finish
it. If you believe that there is at
least a 5% chance that crypto is going
to benefit from AI agents and as a AI
agents grow, they're going to be nuding
this and the ecosystem is going to
continue to grow because tokenization is
going to happen or else it's going to
go. What is your position in Bitcoin?
What is your position in crypto? If it's
zero right now, do you think there's at
least a 5% chance that it happens? If
you think there's a 5% chance, you
should have 5% of your money in it in my
opinion. That's my opinion. That is not
advice for you. But for everyone out
there who's thinking about this, if you
think there's a 10% chance it should
happen, I think you should have a 10%
chance. If you're looking to make money
because you have money or because you're
young and you have time to make back
money you can lose and you want to put
more, that's your choice. I do believe
that right now is a good riskreward. If
we take out the lows, I'm out. I don't
want to be involved anymore until we go
back and we break back above the 200 day
moving average. But for now, that's what
I believe. That's how I get to those
thoughts.
Disclosures.
Again, read them on your own. I'm not
here to guarantee things. I'm not here
to have you buy the names that I buy. I
trade them. I'm involved in them. For
the RAAS, reach out. Remember, go to
viser-labs, visserylabs.com.
You can find out how to get involved.
But remember, it is important right now
for you to be involved in AI agents and
to be involved in crypto. I will start
my AI plus crypto YouTube which will be
separate. It'll go up and go up to
subscribers beginning towards the end of
the month. For now guys, have a great
weekend and I will see you next